从未想过我们会在这儿面对面
Never thought we’d be here
如同几英里之外
Face to face miles away
在人群中认出你
With you of all people
从没想过会发生这种情况
Never thought I’d see the day
我早该离开你
I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
从未有如此痛苦
Never knew an ache like this
如影随形
It goes with me wherever I go
从未离开
It never leaves, it always is
反复提醒我
Reminds me what I already know
早就该离开你
Should’ve left you
我早该离开你
I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
亲爱的 你让我发疯
Oh baby, you made me lose my mind
我这一路以来只发现
I came all this way only to find
我不得不迁就更差的情况
I had to get so low
你知道我早该离开你
You know I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
曾经的梦想和希望
Dreams and hopes of happy days
曾占据我的脑海
Use to occupy my mind
但看看现在发生了什么
But now all I see is how in those days
我当时真是非常盲目
I’ve been so painfully blind
我早该离开你
I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
从未想过你会浪费我的时间
Never thought you‘d be a waste of my time
我曾认为时间由我掌控 然而不是
Was sure time was on my side, no
当其他钟表走得飞快的时候
While all other clocks were ticking so fast
我的走得太慢
Mine was going too slow
我早该离开你
I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
亲爱的 你让我发疯
Oh baby, you made me lose my mind
我这一路以来只发现
I came all this way only to find
我不得不迁就更差的情况
I had to get so low
你知道我早该离开你
You know I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
亲爱的 你让我发疯
Oh baby, you made me lose my mind
我这一路以来只发现
I came all this way only to find
我不得不迁就更差的情况
I had to get so low
你知道我早该离开你
You know I should’ve left you
而且越早越好
A long time ago
我早该离开你
I should’ve left you
比冰河时代还要早
A long ice time ago